[
  {
    "Front": "λαγχάνω",
    "Back": " vb. ureg.: får, vinder"
  },
  {
    "Front": "λαµβάνω",
    "Back": " vb. ureg.: tager, får"
  },
  {
    "Front": "λαµπρός",
    "Back": " adj. 1-2: strålende"
  },
  {
    "Front": "λανθάνω",
    "Back": " vb. ureg.: er skjult"
  },
  {
    "Front": "λέγω",
    "Back": " vb.: siger"
  },
  {
    "Front": "λείπω",
    "Back": " vb. ureg.: forlader"
  },
  {
    "Front": "λευκός",
    "Back": " adj. 1-2: hvid"
  },
  {
    "Front": "λήγω",
    "Back": " vb.: holder op"
  },
  {
    "Front": "λίθος",
    "Back": " sb. 2 m.: sten"
  },
  {
    "Front": "λιµήν",
    "Back": " sb. 3 m.: havn"
  },
  {
    "Front": "λογίζοµαι",
    "Back": " vb.: beregner"
  },
  {
    "Front": "λογικός",
    "Back": " adj. 1-2: logisk"
  },
  {
    "Front": "λογισµός",
    "Back": " sb. 2 m.: beregning"
  },
  {
    "Front": "λόγος",
    "Back": " sb. 2 m.: tale, fornuft"
  },
  {
    "Front": "λοιπός",
    "Back": " adj. 1-2: resterende"
  },
  {
    "Front": "λυπέω",
    "Back": " vb.: giver sorg"
  },
  {
    "Front": "λύπη",
    "Back": " sb. 1 f.: sorg"
  },
  {
    "Front": "λυπηρός",
    "Back": " adj. 1-2: besværlig"
  },
  {
    "Front": "λύσις",
    "Back": " sb. 3 f.: løsnen"
  },
  {
    "Front": "λύω",
    "Back": " vb.: løser"
  }
]